{
    "subject": "resource/The_Friends_of_Distinction",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "The Friends of Distinction are from United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8212478160858154,
            "question": "Where are the Friends of Distinction from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7546391487121582,
            "question": "Are the Friends of Distinction from a specific nation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7334645986557007,
            "question": "Is the musical group Friends of Distinction American?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7169907093048096,
            "question": "What country are the Friends of Distinction associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7049692273139954,
            "question": "Where did the Friends of Distinction originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6902999877929688,
            "question": "To which country do the Friends of Distinction belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6719138026237488,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the origin of the Friends of Distinction?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5874592065811157,
            "question": "The Friends of Distinction, what is their nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2910918891429901,
            "question": "What is the country of origin for the musical group Friends of Distinction?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2554391920566559,
            "question": "What is the nationality of the musical group Friends of Distinction?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Friends of Distinction are from United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9199_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the country of origin for the musical group Friends of Distinction?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9199_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Friends of Distinction, what is their nationality?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9199_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about the origin of the Friends of Distinction?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9199_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9199_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9199_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9199_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9199_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9199_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9199_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9199_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9199_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9199_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9199_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that all four documents mention that the group was formed in Los Angeles (which is part of the United States) in 1968, and one document even mentions that they toured the United States and its territories."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the formation and history of The Friends of Distinction, indicating that they were an American vocal group. This supports the statement that The Friends of Distinction are from the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}